

SAM SUNNY

Fullstack Web Developer

CONTACT



Alte Landstrasse 189 8708 Mannedorf Zurich,Switzerland +41 762147703



samsunny101@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/samsunny101

GitHub

https://github.com/samsunny001

Website



https://samsunny001.github.io

PERSONAL INFO

Date of birth

04.11.1989

Nationality

Indian

Work Permit

В

LANGUAGES

English

Native

German

Beginner

Hindi

Fluent

INTERESTS

- Making website and image editing.
- Solving complex coding issues

PROFILE / SUMMARY

I am Full Stack Web developer almost three years of work experience. Excellent team member and problem solver. Good communicator according to the client requirement, interacts effectively with team mates and clients. Taking back end of whole project according to client instructions and also updating / maintenance the project according to client instructions. Well behave in the team.

Strong Knowledge in PHP Programming language, SQL, MySQL, framework Codelgniter. For front end development HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQuery knows very well. Expert level skill in Excel, Word, FileZilla, Gimp, Photoshop CS3, Balsamiq mockups, GitHub and have little knowledge in C Programming language and very good in software testing.

I want to be part of dynamic, motivated workforce in a team-oriented organization, in which my skills can be put to optimal use.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Web development
- Data structures
- Database design
- Making responsive websites
- Designing
- Making mockups
- Software Testing
- Use of Github

TECH STACK

Languages: PHP, JavaScript, C, SQL

Databases: MySQL

Frameworks: Codelgniter, Balsamiq wire frames

Software: Microsoft SQL Server, Eclipse, Netbeans, Windows expression.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology in Information Technology Toc H Institute of Science and Technology (Kerala, India) 80/2008 - 11/2012

Graduate diploma in Information Technology
Wellington Institute of Technology (Wellington, New Zealand)
03/2017 - 11/2017

WORK EXPERIENCE / PROJECTS

Casual worker Printlink • Wellington, New Zealand

11/2017 – 01/2019 I worked in New Zealand largest printing company.

My job consisted in sorting out New Zealand students exam papers

according to the different subject.

The company is mainly functioning in Python Programming Language.

PHP developer/Tester Wellington Institute of Technology • Wellington, New Zealand

07/2017 - 11/2017 As part of my studies I done project called "Student Alumni System"

It's mainly developed using PHP programming language (CodeIgniter

frame work) back end is MySQL.

Test whole project using manual way.

Sabbatical Diverse studies • Wellington, New Zealand

01/2017 – 06/2017 Improving my skills in web development and moved to wellington New

Zealand.

PHP Programmer Invis Multimedia Private Limited • Kerala, India

11/2015 – 12/2016 I worked in this company as a freelancer.

PHP Programmer Invis Multimedia Private Limited • Kerala, India

07/2014 - 10/2015 Doing code using PHP programming language.

Managing the front end work using CSS and HTML.

Updating and maintenance of the project according to client requirements.

Client discussion

Backups taking for customer needs.

Adding project using FileZilla

Database MySQL.

PHP Developer Dayscholars Innovation Private limited • Kerala, India

09/2013 – 07/2014 Developing the program using PHP

Image editing using GIMP tools

To identify potential targets for the organization Front end design using HTML,CSS and Bootstrap.

Decision maker, active member

Use od Github.

Manage the time schedule and good communicator.

Sam Sunny 2/3

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

Certifications

2013 Java Certification.

2017 - 2017 Graduate diploma in Information Technology

Publications

2019 Website Created in Github.

Link: https://samsunny001.github.io

Sam Sunny 3/3